class DataBase {
  static List<Map<String, dynamic>> myData = [
    {
      "question":
          "Which programming language is commonly used for Flutter app development?",
      "options": ["Kotlin", "Swift", "Dart", "C++"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the framework used to build cross-platform mobile apps in Flutter?",
      "options": ["React Native", "Xamarin", "Flutter", "Ionic"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which technology is Flutter known for making it easier to create beautiful mobile apps?",
      "options": ["Material Design", "Widgets", "SwiftUI", "Bootstrap"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many types of widgets are there in flutter?",
      "options": ["2", "1", "5", "4"],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the Flutter widget that represents the basic building block of the user interface?",
      "options": ["Blocks", "Widgets", "Elements", "Components"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the primary purpose of the 'pubspec.yaml' file in a Flutter project?",
      "options": [
        "To store user data",
        "To manage project dependencies",
        "To define app icons",
        "To write documentation"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What is the Flutter feature used for creating responsive layouts for various screen sizes?",
      "options": [
        "Flexbox",
        "Responsive Design",
        "Media Queries",
        "Grid Layout"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which IDE (Integrated Development Environment) is commonly used for Flutter app development?",
      "options": ["Visual Studio Code", "Eclipse", "Xcode", "Android Studio"],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Hot Reload' in Flutter allow developers to do?",
      "options": [
        "Reboot the device",
        "Recompile the entire app",
        "Instantly view code changes",
        "Delete code files"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Which platform can you target with Flutter for app development?",
      "options": ["Windows", "macOS", "iOS", "All of the above"],
      "answer": 3
    },
  ];
}
